(xylophone music begins)
♪ I don't want a lot for Christmas ♪
♪ There is just one thing I need ♪
♪ I don't care about the presents ♪
♪ Underneath the Christmas tree ♪
♪ I just want you for my own ♪
♪ More than you could ever know ♪
♪ Make my wish come true ♪
♪ All I want for Christmas ♪
♪ is you, ♪
♪ yeah ♪
♪ I don't want a lot for Christmas ♪
♪ There is just one thing I need ♪
♪ And I ♪
♪ Don't care about the presents ♪
♪ Underneath the Christmas tree ♪
♪ I don't need to hang my stocking ♪
♪ There upon the fireplace (Ah) ♪
♪ Santa Claus won't make me happy ♪
♪ With a toy on Christmas Day ♪
♪ I just want you for my own (Ooh) ♪
♪ More than you could ever know (Ooh) ♪
♪ Make my wish come true ♪
♪ All I want for Christmas is you ♪
♪ You, baby ♪
♪ Oh, I won't ask for
much this Christmas ♪
♪ I won't even wish for snow (And I) ♪
♪ I'm just gonna keep on waiting ♪
♪ Underneath the mistletoe ♪
♪ I won't make a list and send it ♪
♪ To the North Pole for Saint Nick (Ah) ♪
♪ I won't even stay awake to ♪
♪ Hear those magic reindeer click ♪
♪ 'Cause I just want
you here tonight (Ooh) ♪
♪ Holding on to me so tight (Ooh) ♪
♪ What more can I do? ♪
♪ Oh baby, all I want
for Christmas is you ♪
♪ You, baby ♪
♪ Ah, Oh, all the lights are shining ♪
♪ So brightly everywhere
(So brightly, baby) ♪
♪ And the sound of children's ♪
♪ Laughter fills the air (Oh, oh yeah) ♪
♪ And everyone is singing (Oh yeah) ♪
♪ I hear those sleigh bells ringing (Oh) ♪
♪ Santa, won't you bring me ♪
♪ the one I really need? (Yeah, oh, oh) ♪
♪ Won't you please bring my baby to me? ♪
♪ Oh, I don't want a lot for Christmas ♪
♪ This is all I'm asking for (Ah) ♪
♪ I just wanna see my baby ♪
♪ Standing right outside my door ♪
♪ Oh, I just want you for my own (Ooh) ♪
♪ More than you could ever know (Ooh) ♪
♪ Make my wish come true ♪
♪ Oh baby, all I want
for Christmas is you ♪
♪ You, baby ♪
♪ All I want for Christmas
is you, baby (You) ♪
♪ All I want for Christmas is
you, baby (Ah, oh, ah, oh) ♪
♪ All I want for Christmas
is you, baby (You) ♪
♪ All I want for Christmas is you, baby ♪
♪ All I Want ♪
(music fades out)